Now we will have the reading of the law
found in Exodus the 20th chapter verses
1-1
17.
Okay, go ahead. And God spake all these
words, saying, I am the Lord thy God,
which I brought thee out of the land of
Egypt, out of the house of bondage. Thou
shall have no other gods before me. Thou
shalt not make unto thee any graven
image, or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above, or that is in the
earth beneath, or that is in the water
under the earth. Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them, nor serve them. For I,
the Lord thy God, am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children, unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me,
AND SHOWING MERCY UNTO THOUSANDS OF them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain, for the Lord would not
hold him guiltless that taketh his name
in vain. Remember the Sabbath day to
keep it holy. Six days shalt thou labor
and do all thy work. But the seventh day
is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In
it thou shalt not do any work. Thou nor
thy son, nor thy daughter, thy man's
servant, nor thy maid servant, nor thy
cattle, nor thy stranger that is within
thy gates. For in six days the Lord made
heaven and earth, the sea, and all that
in them is, and rested the seventh day.
Wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day, and hallowed it. Honor thy father
and thy mother, that thy days may be
long upon the land which the Lord thy
God giveth thee. Thou shalt not kill.
Thou shalt not commit adultery. Thou
shall not steal. Thou shall not bear
false witness against thy neighbor. Thou
shall not covet. Thou thy neighbor's
house. Thou shalt not coveret thy
neighbor's wife, nor his man's servant,
nor his maid servant, nor his ox, nor
his ass, nor anything that is thy
neighbor's.
>> Let's go in Ecclesiastes the 12th
chapter.
Read verses 13 and 14.
Go ahead.
>> Let us hear the conclusion of the whole
matter. Fear God and keep his
commandments, for this is the whole duty
of man. For God shall bring every work
into judgment with every secret thing,
whether it be good or whether it be
evil.
>> Let's go into Revelation chapter 22,
read verses 14 and 15.
Go ahead. Blessed are they that do his
commandments, that they may have right
to the tree of life, and may enter in
through the gates into the city. For
without are dogs, and sorcerers, and
whoreongers, and murderers, and
idolattors, and whosoever loveth and
maketh a lie. We want to thank God for
the reading of the law.
Good afternoon. And as always, it's good
to stand before you on the Lord's
Sabbath day.
You know sisters and brothers,
the title of this lesson,
the gospel by the prophet Zachchariah.
It was
put together through the grace of God
by me because you get New Testament
Christians
is telling you that the Old Testament
and prophecy have been fulfilled.
And the Lord called me to put together
and show you
that that's not the case.
You know, every prophet
preached the gospel.
I could have gone to Daniel and dealt
with this. I could have gone to
Jeremiah, Isaiah,
and gave the same lesson
because all of them preached the gospel
of the kingdom of God. That's the gospel
of the coming of the kingdom of God.
And by the time you get out of prophecy,
there is nothing else left.
So we're going to work with this and
we're going to show you how that the
prophets called it before the apostles.
So if you call yourself a New Testament
Christian,
you are no Christian at all.
Because sisters and brothers, the Lord
said to the law and to the testimony,
>> right? to the law and to the testimony.
If they don't speak according to this,
there is no light in them. In other
words, they don't have no understanding.
So, we're going to So, I call I chose
to preach the gospel, put together the
gospel out of the book of the prophet
Zachchariah.
And we going to see
if all this stuff that we going to deal
with this afternoon have been fulfilled
and who told about it first. We're going
to start this in Zechariah the first
chapter.
Zechariah chapter 1
and we're going to start reading at
verse 7. Zechariah chapter 1
and verse 7.
Okay, go ahead. Upon the 4 and 20th day
of the 11th month, which is the month
Shabbat, in the second year of Darius,
came the word of the Lord unto
Zachchariah, the son of Barekiah, the
son of Edido the prophet, saying,
>> Uhhuh. I saw by night, and behold, a man
riding upon a red horse, and he stood
among the myrtle trees that were in the
bottom, and behind him were there red
horses, speckled and white.
>> Uh-huh. Then said I, "Oh my Lord, what
up? What are these?" And the angel that
talked with me said unto me, I will show
thee what these be. Now, right here, the
Lord letting you know that he had these
four angels. He he brought him all kind
of in in in different forms like men
riding horses and everything else.
These four angels are what the Lord is
using to keep this earth in check. So he
said, "What are these?" Go ahead and
read
>> verse 10. And the man that stood among
the myrtle trees answered and said,
"These are they whom the Lord has sent
to walk to and fro through the earth."
>> Now he sent him to walk to and fro on
the earth. But man think that he is
causing stuff to go on. Look, you doing
little stuff, but the Lord is not going
to let you get too far out of check,
right? These angels here to keep it in
order.
And when you have some real drama,
that's because the angels
have stepped back by the commandment of
God. Go ahead and read. And they
answered the angel of the Lord that
stood among the myrtle trees and said,
"We have walked to and fro through the
earth, and behold, all the earth sitth
still, and is at rest." Now, he said,
"We didn't walk to and fro in the earth,
and the whole earth is at still and is
at rest."
These angels know because they made it
that way. Yes. At the commandment of
God. Go ahead and read. Then the angel
of the Lord answered and said, "Oh Lord
of hosts, how long will thou not have
mercy on Jerusalem and on the cities of
Judah against which thou hast had
indignation these three score and 10
years?" So
this one angel looked and said, "The
whole land of rest, but still you got
Judah and Israel is in trouble."
>> Yes, they're in captivity all over the
world. And he said, "How long will you
have indignation against them these 70
years?" Because now that that was during
the time
of the Persian Empire.
>> Yes. Because it started under the
Babylonian Empire. And what did the Lord
say? What verse
>> we had 13?
>> Uh-huh.
>> And the Lord answered the angel that
talked with me with good words and
comfortable words.
>> Go ahead. So the angel that communed
with me said unto me, cry thou, saying,
Thus said the Lord of hosts, I am
jealous for Jerusalem and for Zion with
great jealousy. And he is still jealous,
sisters and brothers. And the world
going to find that out cuz they think
that the Lord throw his people away, but
he haven't. Go ahead and read.
>> And I am very sore displeased with the
heathen that are at ease. Go ahead.
>> For I was but a little displeased, and
they helped forth the affliction. So he
said I am very displeased with the
nations. That's what heathen is that are
displeased.
So I
was just a little displeased but they
have furthered
the affliction. Yes.
Like when they sent him here show we was
going to be slave but we didn't have to
be hung on trees. We didn't have to be
beat continually. We didn't have to have
our males castrated teach
and all this other stuff like boiling in
the pot. The Lord didn't want all that
to happen. He just wanted you to come
over here and make us work to show his
displeasure for somebody else.
>> He said, "But you have further the
affliction." That mean you you made you
a debt partner that you going to have to
pay.
>> Go ahead and read
>> 16. Therefore, thus sayeth the Lord, I
am returned to Jerusalem with mercies.
>> My house shall be built in it, sayeth
the Lord of hosts. Go ahead. And a line
shall be stretched forth upon Jerusalem.
>> So, I will return and we're going to
show you that.
And Jerusalem going to be built again,
but this time for the people of
Jerusalem.
>> Yes.
>> Not the people that say they are Jews.
Go ahead and read.
>> Quiet yet, saying, Thus said the Lord of
hosts. Go ahead. My cities through
prosperity shall yet be spread abroad
and the Lord shall yet come for Zion and
shall yet to Jerusalem.
>> And that is in the future, sisters and
brother. But nobody taught this because
we the world have been taught by the
Gentiles because we are in the times of
the Gentiles and which I'm going to show
you in the next lesson that we have. So
all you have been brought to you by the
Gentiles. But the Lord said, "These 70
years, what that you've been pleased,
where did these 70 years come from?"
What 70 years? Let's go. And we're going
to see what's going to happen at the end
of these 70 years because we have a
lesson that's called the 70 weeks of
Daniel.
The Lord turned that from 70 years to 70
weeks of years. And we have a lesson to
show you,
which we're going to point some out in
this lesson, that once that time is up,
the world got a problem.
Let's go into Daniels the 25th chapter.
>> Jeremiah Jeremiah, I'm sorry. Jeremiah
the 25th chapter.
When those 70 years are over, sisters
and brothers,
the world going to get something they
ain't been looking for.
Jeremiah 25, we're going to start
reading at verse one. Jeremiah 25 and
verse one.
25 and one.
Okay, go ahead.
>> The word that came to Jeremiah
concerning all the people of Judah in
the fourth year of Jehookim, the son of
Josiah, king of Judah, that was the
first year of Nebuchadnezzar, king of
Babylon. Now this was this word came
while Israel still while the Judah was
still in Jerusalem sisters and brethren
because Nebuchadnezzar has his first
year so he hadn't moved on anybody yet
because Nebuchadnezzar is the one that
took out the three tribes Benjamin,
Judah, and Levi. The Assyrians took out
the nine tribes. Yes. Go ahead and read.
to which Jeremiah the prophet spake unto
all the people of Judah and to all the
inhabitants of Jerusalem, saying,
>> Go ahead.
>> From the 13th year of Josiah, the son of
Ammon, king of Judah, even until this
day, that is the 3 and 20th year, the
word of the Lord has come unto me, and I
have spoken unto you, rising early and
speaking, but you have not hearkened. He
said, "Now, all of this time I've been
rising up and speaking to you early in
the morning, and you have not listened
to me, cuz the Lord did not want to take
Judah out of the land." He wanted to
keep a representative in there, but they
didn't listen. Skip now to verse seven.
Verse seven, go ahead.
>> Yet you have not hearkened unto me,
sayeth the Lord, that you might provoke
me to anger with the works of your hands
to your own hurt. Now, we're the one
that pro provoked God to anger by
serving other gods and get involved with
all kind of riches and stuff, but it was
to our hurt. Didn't he say it?
>> Yes, sir.
But we didn't believe it. So, what did
he do? Go ahead and read.
>> Therefore, thus sayeth the Lord of
hosts, because you have not heard my
words.
>> Behold, I will send and take all the
families of the north, sayeth the Lord.
Go ahead. and Nebuchadnezzar the king of
Babylon, my servant, and will bring them
against this land, and against the
inhabitants thereof, and against all
these nations round about, and will
utterly destroy them, and make them an
astonishment, and a hissing, and a
perpetual desolation. Now, who is the
one that the Lord that that caused the
Lord to do this? We did. It wasn't the
strangers. That's why I'm not like my
other Hebrew brothers. I am not mad at
white folks teach. I'm not mad at
Hamites. I'm not mad at anybody because
I know the soul where the I know from
whence the source of my punishment came.
>> And I know that it didn't have to do be
this way. All I had to do was obey.
>> And it wasn't hard to obey. The Lord
didn't give us nothing. He didn't say
you have to climb a mountain and swim a
do what I say.
>> Yes.
>> Go ahead and read
>> verse 10. Moreover, I will take from
them the voice of mirth and the voice of
gladness.
>> So, I'm going to bring the kingdom of
Nebuchadnezzar and all the kings that
are north against you. I'm going to take
away from you the voice of gladness and
mirth. Go ahead and read.
>> The voice of the bridegroom and the
voice of the bride, the sound of the
millstones and the light of the candles.
Go ahead.
>> And this whole land shall be a
desolation and an astonishment. And
these nations shall serve the king of
Babylon 70 years. And that's exactly
what they did. But that's the 70 years.
That was the Babylon the old king of
Babylon, Nebuchadnezzar
and his son Belshock.
>> Yes.
>> But we going to show you. Let's go just
a bit a little bit beyond 70 years. Go
ahead and read verse 12. And it shall
come to pass when 70 years are
accomplished that I will punish the king
of Babylon and that nation sayeth the
Lord for their iniquity and the land of
the calans and will make it perpetual
desolation.
>> So when the seven years seven years 70
years over it, I'm going to punish that
land, the land of the called in. But go
ahead and read. and I will bring upon
that land all my words which I have
pronounced against it, even all that is
written in this book which Jeremiah has
prophesied against all the nations.
>> See now, not only did Judah bring did we
bring punishment on us, now because our
misbehaving and God had to use the
stranger to punish us because of our
misbehavior. Then he got overzealous.
Now the Lord going to punish him. If the
people really understood who really
brought this ugly on the earth, they'd
be mad at us every day.
So when is it all going to end? Go ahead
and read. For many nations and great
kings shall serve themselves of them
also, and I will recompense them
according to their deeds and according
to the works of their own hands. He
said, "Now many nations are going to set
themselves on Nebuchadnezzar, upon
Babylon,
and great kings."
You know what that did? That took it
beyond Babylon of the old days, that
took it to the future. Yes. Let me show
you how the old Babylon,
Nebuchadnezzar's Babylon, came to an
end. Yes. Let's go into Daniel the 5th
chapter.
Daniel's chapter 5.
cuz the Lord has laid this thing out. So
until all you got to do is read this.
Cuz I was reading and I said, "Wait a
minute. Wait a minute.
This Babylon didn't end like the book
said it was going to end.
The Lord say he going to bring many
nations and great kings to take Babylon
down."
So when I read this, I said, "There's
something more to this that I've been
missing." Yeah, we're going to start it
at verse one. Daniel's 5 and verse one.
Daniel's 5 and1. Okay, go ahead.
>> Belazar the king made a great feast to a
thousand of his lords.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And drank wine before the thousand.
>> Now this is Nebuchadnezzar's son. We
read this on Pentecost. But sometime you
have to read the same other same stuff
to go in a further direction. Y'all
understand?
>> Yes sir.
>> Now this guy he having he having a ball.
Go ahead and read. Belazza while he
tasted the wine commanded to bring the
golden and silver vessels which his
father Nebuchadnezzar had taken out of
the temple which was in Jerusalem. Go
ahead.
>> That the king and his princes, his
wives, and his concubines might drink
therein.
>> Big mistake. Go ahead and read.
>> Then they brought the golden vessels
that were taken out of the temple of the
house of God which was at Jerusalem. And
the king and his princes, his wives, and
his concubines drank in them.
>> They show you. Boy, he didn't know
nothing about the God of Israel.
>> Oh, he did. That's some scary stuff he
did there. Let me show you how scary.
What verse?
>> Verse four.
>> Go ahead. They drank wine and praised
the gods of gold and of silver, of
brass, of iron. Go ahead.
>> Of wood and of stone, material stuff.
That's what the Gentiles are still
because Nebuchadnezzar was a gentile.
Yes. In the Babylonian, they are still
they go is money teach. It's all that
simple.
>> So they praise the God of material
stuff. And the God in whose hand their
breath was in, they didn't even mention.
Go ahead and read. In the same hour came
four fingers of a man's hand and wrote
over against the candlestick upon the
plaster of the wall of the king's
palace. Now they party and praise and
material stuff. All of a sudden uh
fingers of a hand jumped up. Poof. That
got somebody's attention. Go ahead and
read.
>> And the king saw the part of the hand
that wrote. Then the king's countenance
was changed
>> and his thoughts troubled him.
>> Go ahead.
>> So that the joints of his loins were
loosed and his knees smoke one against
another. He pretty scared, wasn't it?
Yeah.
>> I don't been scared. I remember years
ago when I got so scared of something,
my knees was knocking and I couldn't
stop them.
That's scary. You scared then? Go ahead
and read. The king cried aloud to bring
IN THE ASTROLOGERS, THE CALS and the
soothsayers. And the king spake and said
to the wise men of Babylon, "Whosoever
shall read this writing, and show me the
interpretation thereof shall be clothed
with scarlet, and have a chain of gold
about his neck, and shall be the third
ruler in the kingdom." Look, sisters and
brothers, he said that, but none of his
wise men could answer that.
Don't you know the world is still in
that condition? If we don't come to
Israel, they don't know. Ain't nobody
talking about
Jesus coming to the earth. You talking
about being stole off the earth and
taken to heaven.
>> Yeah.
People don't know. You didn't heard
every now and then somebody speak about
the great tribulation, but people don't
know about that. They don't know about
Armageddon. They don't know that the
Lord is going to actually assault this
earth with his army.
and you ain't going nowhere.
Skip down to verse 13 and read it. Then
was Daniel brought in before the king.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the king spake and said unto Daniel,
"Art thou that Daniel, which are the
children of the captivity of Judah,
>> whom the king my father brought out of
jury?"
>> Go ahead. I have even I have even heard
of thee, that the spirit of God is in
thee, and that life and understanding
and excellent wisdom is found in thee.
Uh-huh. And now, now look, sisters and
brothers,
he brought in his people. They couldn't
answer that. So his mother told him,
"So, look, you got somebody in your
kingdom that can
>> Yeah.
>> Daniel.
God speaks to him." So what she do? She
went and I mean what he did? He called
Daniel. What verse were we?
>> That was the end of 13. Okay. Skip down
to verse 17 and go ahead. Then Daniel
answered and said
>> and and he called Daniel and look what
Daniel said. Go ahead and read.
>> And answered and said before the king,
let thy gifts be to thyself.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And give thy rewards to another.
>> Go ahead.
>> Yet I will read the writing unto the
king and make known to him the
interpretation. Look sisters and
brothers, he said anybody do that, he
going to make them th read in the
kingdom and he going to put gain a chain
and neck. He going to give them money.
He said look let your words be to
another. But still, I'm going to tell
you what's going to happen to you,
mister.
Same way, sisters and brothers. All
these ministers with these great big
churches, all of them get paid buying
Cadillacs and all that kind of stuff.
Yeah, I got one,
but I ain't getting paid by you. You
understand? Right.
Big houses, summer home.
when I got I bought it out of my own
labor teach
but the whole thing sisters and brothers
he said look
I'm going to tell you this thing and I
don't even need your gifts what verse
was that the end of 17 skip now to verse
25 he said I'm going to tell it to you
verse 25 go ahead and this is the
writing that was written
>> Uhhuh Many, many tea, you farting.
>> Go ahead.
>> This is the interpretation of the thing.
>> Many God has numbered thy kingdom and
finished it. God have numbered your
kingdom and finished it.
People don't think about that. Go ahead
and read. Tel, thou are weighed in the
balances and are found wanting. The Lord
didn't put you in the balance and you
have been found wanting. In other words,
you come up lacking, mister, go ahead.
>> Paris, thy kingdom is divided and given
to the me and Persians. While he was
living, he told him, your kingdom is
divided and given to the me and the
Persian.
While you are living, what verse was
that?
>> That was the end of 28. Skip down to
verse 30 and let's see what happened.
Go ahead. In that night was Belshazzar,
the king of the of the Calaldans slain.
Next month, that night,
>> six months ago, that night.
>> That very night, cuz he really crossed
the line.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> And Darius the Median took the kingdom,
>> being about three score and two years
old.
>> So the Lord killed him that very night.
that very night sisters and brothers
because and then there's the me took the
kingdom sisters and brothers
and this what you have to know the Lord
to this thing sisters and brothers that
was the end of the Babylonian
Empire.
So when you look at what
Babylon that Jeremiah was talking about
that is called Babylon the great future
Babylon even future to us.
Y'all don't understand.
So D say you can keep your money. You
can keep your reward.
>> Keep it. Uh-huh.
I said the same thing. Keep your money.
Keep your reward. I don't get paid. None
of these teachers get paid. None of us.
We all teaching for salvation. Yes, sir.
And if a brother come up to me and want
to be paid for teaching, I said, "You're
in the wrong place, mister.
>> We're preaching for salvation. You
trying to get money. You go out and get
you a job." There you go.
So, let me show you.
He was speaking of Babylon the Great.
sisters and brothers, one that's to
come. Let's go into Revelation
the 17th chapter and have a look at it.
Revelation chapter 17.
We're going to start reading at verse
one.
Revelation 17 and verse one.
Okay, go ahead. And there came one of
the seven angels which had the seven
vows and talk with me, saying unto
saying unto me, come hither, I will show
unto thee the judgment of the great
that siteth upon many waters. Now,
this is talking about a religion,
sisters and brothers. Great that
sits upon many waters. Actually, that's
the Catholic Church cuz it says he come
from God
and it's lying. God ain't got nothing to
do with. That's Satan's organization.
But go ahead and read. With whom the
kings of the earth have committed
fornication.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the inhabitants of the earth have
been made drunk with the wine of her
fornication. Well, I'm going to tell you
what drunk is. What day is it that the
world hold service and call it a
Christian Sabbath day?
>> Sunday.
First day of the week. the whole world
doing. They've been made drunk with the
wine. That's that bad doctrine. How many
of them churches say you going to
heaven? All of
>> come from the Catholic church. You've
been made drunk. Ain't nobody going to
heaven.
How is you going to get as a second
heaven and then you going to meet Jesus
and you going to come back here? Go
ahead and read verse three. So he
carried me away in the spirit into the
wilderness. And I saw a woman sit upon a
scarlet colored beast. Go ahead.
>> Full of names of blasphemy having seven
heads and 10 horns.
>> Now this woman we going to show you
gentile das sister having seven heads
and 10 horns. Skip down to verse nine
and read it.
And here is the mind which hath wisdom.
Go ahead. The seven heads are seven
mountains on which the woman siteth. Now
all you got to do is find whatever
nation that's built upon seven hills of
seven mountain you going to find Rome.
That's where it is. And in the middle of
Rome is the Catholic Church.
So the that siteth on many waters.
In other words, the false religions says
she's from God and she is not. Go ahead
and read. And there are seven kings.
Five are fallen and one is and the other
is not yet come. And what verse was
that?
>> That was uh verse nine.
>> Verse 10.
>> We have verse 10 now.
>> Okay, we're verse nine. We're going to
skip
>> We missed verse five.
>> We're going to skip now to verse You
missed verse five.
>> We missed verse five.
>> Well, read it.
Don't let me miss nothing. Go ahead.
>> And upon her forehead was a name
written, Mystery Babylon the Great. Now
upon her head was written mystery
Babylon the great. See we missed the
major part right now.
>> Yes sir.
>> Because the old Babylon is gone.
>> But you got a new Babylon now which is
Babylon the great
because it started with old Babylon.
It's going to end with Babylon the great
still under the gentile tutorship. Now
skip down to verse 12. We got to finish
it.
>> I'll finish then. Go ahead.
>> And upon her forehead was a name
written, mystery Babylon the great. Go
ahead.
>> The mother of harlots. Mother of harlots
and abominations of the earth. That
means she got daughters.
What do you think all these other
religions come from that are called
Protestants?
>> Who do you think they came out of?
Mystery Babylon.
I'm the Baptist. What time you go to
church? On Sunday.
Babylon. Babylon the Great.
Methodist. When you go to church on
Sunday. Babylon.
Episcopalian. When you go Babylon.
I go on Sunday. All of these come out of
Babylon the great. And don't you know
right now they in Europe that they are
making Sunday now
on their calendars. They're making
Monday
>> a Monday rather. Now
>> on their calendars is what?
>> First day of the week. That means Sunday
is the Sabbath day. Now
>> did we finish that? We now we at verse
9. Skip down to verse 9 and go ahead.
And here's the mind which have wisdom.
>> Go ahead.
>> The seven heads are seven mountains on
which the woman siteth. Now if you got
wisdom you will s see search see out go
and check out the geography on earth and
you'll find out that Rome is the only
city built on this earth on seven
mountains and in the middle of Rome is
the Catholic church.
That's the one that gave you everything
that you call Christianity now.
>> Yes.
Skip down to verse 12 and go ahead.
>> And the t horns which thou sawest are 10
kings. Go ahead.
>> Which have no have which have received
no kingdom as yet
>> but receive power as kings one hour with
the beast.
>> So now that tell us that 10 nations are
going to rise up sisters and brothers
and they going to rule with this beast
one hour which is three and a half
years.
All we got to do is look around and we
going to find them. What verse we had?
13. Go ahead. These have one mind. Go
ahead. and shall give their power and
strength unto the beast.
>> Go ahead.
>> These shall make war with the lamb, and
the lamb shall overcome them, for he is
lord of lords and king of kings. Now, is
the lamb ain't that Jesus?
>> That's Jesus.
>> Is he here yet?
>> Not yet. That mean we talking future,
don't we?
>> Go ahead and read with me.
>> And they that are with him are called
and chosen and faithful. So, some people
going to come with them. What are these
people going to come up from? The first
resurrection. Go ahead and read.
>> That was the end of 14. The end of 14.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Well, sisters and brothers, to let you
know
that uh this great Babylon the great is
not the old Babylon. It ended.
Then after that cameo Persian Empire.
Yes.
So let's go back to Jeremiah the 25th
chapter
cuz at that time
of Babylon the great is the time when
the Lord is going to deal with the
nations sisters and brothers
but don't nobody talk about this they
want to make everything spiritual
like ain't nothing going go down on this
earth. I'm going to tell you something.
You got a problem because we going to
see this thing. Yeah.
In November, I'll be 84 years old. I'm
going to see it. So, if you know if I'm
going to see it, most of y'all going to
see it. You going to be here.
That's why you better pay some attention
to what you dealing with here.
25.
And we're going to start reading
at verse 15.
Jeremiah 25 and verse 15. See, people
don't understand that the Lord didn't
call this thing
and it's taking place all the time, but
ain't nobody listening because you're
drunk on false religion.
>> Yes.
Verse 15, go ahead. For thus sayith the
Lord God of Israel unto me,
>> "Take the wine cup of his of this fury
at my hand, and cause all the nations to
to to whom I send thee to drink it." He
said, "Now, I want you to get to uh uh
the wine of my fury. I want you to go to
all nation and cause them to drink this
wine, cuz I'm going to bring some on
this world that they ain't ready for."
What verse?
>> We have 16.
>> Uh-huh. And they shall drink.
>> They gonna drink
>> and be moved.
>> And be moved
>> and be mad.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Because of this sword that I will send
among them.
>> Cuz I'm going to bring a sword on them.
I'm going to turn them on one another.
Look at this saber rattling that's going
on. Now
the Lord said, I'm going to bring
something on them.
Skip down to verse 27 and go ahead.
Therefore, thou shalt say unto them,
thus sayith the Lord of hosts, the God
of Israel, drink ye, and be drunken, and
spew, and fall, and rise no more because
of the sword which I will send among
you. Cuz when the Lord come and take
down the nation in the war of
Armageddon, ain't going to be no more
rising of the nation. Go ahead and read.
That was the end of verse 27. Ain't
going to be no more rise of the nation,
sisters and brothers. Go ahead and read.
And it shall be, if they refuse to take
the cup at thine hand to drink, then
shall thou say unto them, thus sayeth
the Lord of Hosts, you shall certainly
drink.
>> Go ahead.
>> For lo, I begin to bring evil on the
city, which is called by my name, and
should you be utterly unpunished. You
shall not be unpunished. For I will call
for a sword upon all the inhabitants of
the earth, sayeth the Lord of hosts. He
said, look, you think you ain't going to
drink of this cup? No, you going to
drink of it. Go drink cuz I am beginning
to bring a sword upon the city that's
called by my name. That's Israel, sister
and brother. And you think that I'm
going to take my people down for they
misbehaving and you going to skip it.
>> It ain't going to happen like that.
I don't care how sweet you try to make
the gospel. It's not going to happen
like that. What verse we had? 30. Go
ahead AND READ. THEREFORE PROPHESY thou
against them all these words, and say
unto them, Go ahead.
>> The Lord shall rule from on high. Go
ahead.
>> And utter his voice from his holy
habitation. Go ahead.
>> He shall mightily roar upon his
habitation.
>> He shall give a shout as they that tread
the great against all the inhabitants of
the earth.
>> I tell you, Jesus going to come and he
going to be extremely violent when he
come.
It going to be so much blood you're
going to be up to the horse's brow. Yes,
sir. Skip down to verse 33 and read it.
And the slain of the Lord shall be at
that day from one end of the earth even
until the other end of the earth. THEY
SHALL NOT BE LAMENTED, NEITHER GATHERED
nor buried. They shall be as dung upon
the ground.
>> You didn't hear nothing like this in the
church that you came.
>> I did not.
This going to happen, sisters and
brothers.
>> That's when the Lord come. Everybody be
so glad when Christ come. I'm waiting.
And they even got that messed up. I'm
waiting for the rapture. If you going to
be raptured off, then why is he coming?
>> So what time is it that the Lord is
going to do this? At his coming. Let's
go into Revelation the 19th chapter.
Make it plain.
See, and we starting all this out of
starting all this out of the book of
Zechariah, sisters and brothers.
Cuz all of the
prophets preached the gospel, that is
the coming of the kingdom of God. And
the kingdom of God is not going to come
all peaceful and cuddly. It's going to
come extremely violent. Yes, sir.
Revelation 19, we're going to start
reading at verse 11. Revelation 19 and
verse 11. I'll be glad when Christ come.
Will you?
Let's see if you ready for this. Verse
11. Go ahead. And I saw heaven open, and
behold, a white horse, and he that sat
upon him was called faithful and true.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And in righteousness he do judge and
make war. He ain't coming to talk soft
to you now. Heaven open the book tell
you the heaven going to roll back like a
scroll.
>> Yes.
>> Tell you in revelation also tell you in
Isaiah
and say he's on a white horse and he
ain't coming to talk soft to you. Go
ahead and read.
>> His eyes were as a flame of fire. Go
ahead.
>> And on his head were many crowns. Go
>> And he had a name written that no man
knew but he himself.
>> Go ahead.
>> And he was clothed with a VESTURE DIPPED
IN BLOOD.
>> Whose blood? mind's blood. Go ahead and
read.
>> And his name is called the Word of God.
>> Go ahead. And the armies which were with
him and the armies which were in heaven
followed him up on white horses. Go
ahead.
>> Clothes in fine linen, white and clean.
Now, not only the army going from
heaven, that's the twothirds of the
angels that didn't follow Satan, they
going to all come with him. And also and
the people in the first resurrection
going to meet him in the air and we
going to come with it.
>> Yes, sir.
>> And we ain't coming to kiss people on
the jaw.
>> What verse?
>> We have 15.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And out of his mouth goeth the SH's
sword
>> that with it HE SHOULD SMITE THE
NATIONS.
>> THAT'S HIS WORD. It tell he going to
tell the angels and his servant, kill
them all.
>> He going to smite the nation. Go ahead
and read. And he shall rule them with a
rod of iron. That mean when he come it
ain't going to be no fooling around. You
gonna do what I say or you gonna die.
>> That's a rod of iron. Go ahead and read.
>> And he treaded the wine press of the
fierceness and wrath of almighty God.
What do you think this wine press is?
People
during the war of Armageddon. Just like
in the old days when they made wine,
they take the shoes off and they put
grapes in there and they would tread it
until the juice come out. That was the
wine that he made the wine with. He
going to do it with the fiercest of the
almighty God. What verse
>> we have? 16.
>> Go ahead.
>> And he has on his vesture and on his
thigh a name written. Go ahead.
>> King of kings and lord of lords.
>> That's that sweet Jesus you've been
lying on about. Go ahead and read. And I
saw an angel standing in the sun, and he
cried with a loud voice, saying to all
the fowls that fly in the midst of
heaven, "Come and gather yourselves
together unto the supper of the great
God." Look, the Lord going to kill so
many men until he going to bring the
canals, birds, the buzzers, the
vultures, and everything. And other
scripture let you know he going to bring
the meat eatating lions and tigers and
everything. Yes. To the great supper of
the Lord. Why? Because they going to
kill so many that ain't going to have
enough men to bury them.
Keep reading. That you may eat the flesh
of kings and the flesh of captains and
the flesh of mighty men and the flesh of
horses of them that sit on them and the
flesh of all men, both free and bond,
both small and great. So we ain't coming
to eat nothing but the flesh of men,
SISTERS AND BROTHER. ALL OF THEM, SMALL
AND GREAT, because everybody going to be
involved in this thing. Go ahead and
read.
>> And I saw the beast and the kings of the
earth. Now, who is the beast? That's the
man that's going to be the head of the
European Union,
>> which are the 10 toes in the second
chapter of Daniel and in the 10 horns
and 13 and 17 chapter Revelation. So,
they're going to be leading this. And
who's going to be calling the shot? The
pope.
No, he's the holy man. Yeah, right. Keep
read. And I saw the beast and the kings
of the earth and their armies gathered
together to make war against him that
sat on the horse and against his army.
Go ahead.
>> And the beast was taken, and with him
the false prophet that wrought miracles
before him, with which he deceived them
that had received the mark of the beast,
and them that worship his image.
>> Go ahead. These both were cast alive
into a lake of fire burning with
brimstone. So the beast which is the man
that's going to be running the European
Union and the false prophet which is the
Par wrong they are not going to die like
other men. Lord just going to grab them
and deposit them in the lake of fire
just like that.
And they ain't going to burn up. They
going to be burn. In fact they going to
burn forever. And they going to get
there before the ones that the Lord
created the lake of firef which was
Satan and his angel. Go ahead and read.
>> And the remnant was slain with the sword
of him that set upon the horse. Go
ahead.
>> Which sword proceeded out of his mouth
and all the fowls were filled with their
flesh. So that's why the Lord call for
all these conv cannivorous blur uh uh uh
uh fh uh birds and all the canvas uh uh
beasts in the other scripture because
they going to have so many people that's
going to get killed in this war which is
the war of Armageddon until it's going
to take these animals to eat all these
bodies.
And you didn't know about this? No. And
you've been in church most of your life.
Yep.
You've been woefully misinformed.
Now, let's go into Zechariah, back to
Zechariah the first chapter.
Because in Zechariah, the Lord
showed how all this is going to happen.
And we're going to start at verse 18.
Zechariah 1
and verse 18.
Because they answer because that angel
answered, "Lord, what about Israel that
you've been married with for 70 years,
which turned into 70 weeks of years."
Verse 18,
go ahead.
>> Then lifted I up mine eyes, and saw, and
behold, behold, four horns. And I said
unto the angel that TALKED WITH ME,
"WHAT be these?"
>> Uhhuh.
>> And he answered me, "These are the horns
which have scattered Judah, Israel, and
Jerusalem." So he looked and he saw four
horns
and he asked the angel, "Well, who are
these?" These are the one that scattered
Judah to
Jerusalem and Israel.
Let me show you these four horns. Keep
your marker here. We going to get back.
Keep your marker in Zechariah. We going
to be in Zechariah all afternoon.
So let's go and see who they are. Let's
go into Daniel's the 7th chapter.
Daniel's chapter 7.
So all this scary stuff
and dangerous stuff going to take place
on this earth and you go and sit in any
church tomorrow and see if you going to
hear any of it. None of it.
Sitting every Sunday for a whole year
and see if you going to hear any of it.
None of it.
Seven and uh uh uh and one. Go ahead and
read. In the first year of Belshaza,
king of Babylon, Daniel had a dream and
visions of his head upon his bed. Now,
this is the one that you know that
Belshaz that that drunk that wine out of
the holy cups and got killed. But still
in his first year, Daniel had a dream.
Go ahead and read.
>> Then he wrote the dream and told the sum
of the matters.
>> Go ahead. Daniel spake and said, "I saw
in my vision by night, and behold, the
four winds of the heaven strove upon the
great sea." See, that's why I got the
title of the book that the Lord caused
me to write, the four winds of heaven.
It's these four winds of heaven, they
strove upon the great sea, the sea are
the people. Go ahead. Who are these? Go
ahead and read.
>> And four great beasts came up from the
sea, diverse one from another.
>> Oh, was different. Go ahead and read.
>> The first was like a lion and had
eagle's wings. I beheld till the wings
thereof were plucked and it was lifted
up from the earth and made stand up on
the feet as a man and a man's heart was
given to it. That was Babylon.
And the beast that he called to stand up
was Nebuchadnezzar cuz the Lord brought
some drama and he started praising God
like Daniels did. That's the first one,
the Babylonian sisters and brothers.
They're the one that took out Judah,
Jerusalem.
Go ahead and read. And behold, another
beast, a second, like to a bear, and it
raised up itself on one side, and it had
three ribs in the mouth of it. Go ahead.
>> Between between the teeth of it, and
they said thus unto it, "Arise, devour
much flesh."
>> Now, that's the Meopersian Empire,
sisters and brothers. We was passed on
from Babylon. Remember, Darus took over.
Darus the Aridian took over. Yes.
Babylon. Go ahead and read. After this,
I beheld, and lo, another, like a
leopard, which had upon the back of it
four wings of a foul. The beast had also
four heads, and dominion was given to
it. That was the Greek Empire. Go and
check the table of nations, sisters and
brothers, and you'll find out the
empires came in order just like it
written here. Yes.
Go ahead and read. After this, I saw in
the night visions, and behold, a fourth
beast, go ahead.
>> Dreadful and terrible, and strong
exceedingly, and it had great iron
teeth. It devoured and break in pieces,
and stamped the residue with the feet of
it.
>> Go ahead.
>> And it was diverse from all the beasts
that were before it. And it had 10
horns. Now, this beast is the Roman
Empire. It was really different of all
because not only did he rule you
physically, enslave you, he also
enslaved you mentally and spiritually.
You the world is still enslaved by the
Roman Empire.
>> Yes sir. Where you get Sunday came from
Easter going to heaven Christmas.
You can eat anything you want. All you
got to do is pray over it. All that came
from Rome, sister and brother. The other
one just destroyed you physically, but
they destroyed you spiritually, too.
But who's going to take this kingdom?
Skip down to verse 17. Verse 17 and read
it. These great beasts which are four
Uhhuh.
>> are four kings which shall arise out of
the earth.
>> There's four kingdoms, sisters and
brothers. Babylon first one Meo Persia
Rome uh uh uh Greek uh uh Greece and
Rome in order but what's going to
happen? Go ahead and read
these four
17 vers 17.
>> So these are the four sisters and
brothers that's going that uh uh uh
that's going to have us. Well, well,
Brother Buie, uh, uh, we uh, when we,
uh, uh, when did Judah or the Jews go
into captivity? Go into history. It'll
tell you they went in when the
Babylonians took. And we have been
passed from nation to nation to nation
to nation.
Well, I'm free now, are you? You ain't
got no picture on no dollar bill.
Make it plain.
You drive a car and you have to buy a
license to operate it.
>> You bought a house and you got to pay
taxes. Teach.
If you whip your children too hard, they
make a phone call and DCFS going to come
down on you. You free?
You better give it another thought.
So who are the folk
that took Israel out, that took Judah
out? Babylon, Meo, Persia, Greece, and
Rome. Now let's go back to Zechariah the
first chapter
because Zechariah told it all. That's
why I could have went in Daniels and
preached the same gospel
because the Lord have been preached this
gospel by all his prophets and still
ain't nobody listen
1 and 20. Zechariah 1 and 20.
Okay, read it. And the Lord showed me
four carpenters. And he showed me four
carpenters. Go ahead and read.
>> Then said I, what come these to do?
>> Go ahead. And he spake, saying, "These
are the horns which have scattered
Judah, so that no man did lift up his
head."
>> That's the four that we just got through
talking about. But what this carpet is
going to do? Go ahead.
>> But these are come to fray them.
>> Uh-huh.
>> To cast out the horns of the Gentiles.
>> To cast out the horns of who?
>> The Gentiles.
>> Don't you know that des right here? The
desert.
>> Go ahead.
>> Which lift up their horn over the land
of Judah to scatter it. the Gentiles
scattered Judah. The people that the
world call Jews, I'm talking about the
real ones, us.
But you got these four horns that's
these that's called carpenters. They
going to
take down the nations of the Gentile.
Let's go and look at these carpenters
and what time they go in action. Let's
go into Revelation the 7th chapter.
I mean, Zechariah called it. He called
it. Daniel could have called it.
Isaiah could have called it, but we just
showing you. People talking about the
Old Testament is done away with. Ain't
no more prophecy. I'm just gra I just
grabbed Zechariah just I'm going to get
one of these prophets and show the
difference. I could have went to another
same story.
Revelation 7 chapter and we're going to
start reading at verse one. Revelation 7
and we're going to start reading at
verse one.
Okay, go ahead.
>> And after these things, I saw four
angels standing on the four corners of
the earth, holding the four winds of the
earth, that the wind should not blow on
the earth, nor on the sea, nor on any
tree. So the Lord going to scatter these
four cobters, which are these angels,
sisters and brothers. They're going to
scatter the horns of the Gentiles. In
other words, they going when the Lord
come,
this world is going to still be ruled by
white folks, and it's going to take it
out of their hand. Those are the
Gentiles. What verse we had? Two.
>> Go ahead.
>> And I saw another angel ascending from
the east, having the seal of the living
God.
>> Go ahead.
>> And he cried with a loud voice to the
four angels to whom it was given to hurt
the earth and the sea.
>> Uhhuh. saying, "Hurt not the earth,
neither the sea, nor the trees, till we
have sealed the servants of our God in
their foreheads." Cuz the Lord is
getting ready to bring some real drama
on this earth. This is after the great
tribulation, sisters and brothers, where
the beast and false prophet will have
wre all kind of havoc on anybody that
call upon the name of the true and
living God.
>> Yes. So now the Lord ain't going to let
you be punished by him, too. So he going
to send his angels to seal the ones that
have suffered during the great
tribulation and refuse to rem receive
the mark of the beast which they put on
you every Ash Wednesday.
>> Go ahead and read. And I heard the
number of them that were sealed and
there were sealed 144,000 of all the
tribes of the children of Israel. Go
ahead now. 144,000 that's the children
of Israel. Skip down to verse 9 and read
it.
>> After this, I beheld, and lo, A GREAT
MULTITUDE, WHICH NO MAN could number.
>> Go ahead.
>> of of all nations and kindreds and
people and tongues stood before the
throne and before the Lamb, clothed with
white robes and palms in their hands.
They going to do that when he come. But
that let you know contrary to some of
the teaching of my Hebrew brothers,
Israel is not the only one going to be
saved.
So he sealed 144,000 of Israel, but
there a number that no man could number
out of every kindred, nation, and
tongue. Look like the Lord is saving a
few other people, don't it? That's
right.
Let's go into Revelation 9th chapter.
Yes, sir. Revelation chapter 9. See,
because the Lord is going to bring some
real drama on this earth and he want his
servant seal
cuz you got some Gentiles that's going
to turn and strangers are going to turn
to the true and living God. And when the
Lord get ready to bl pour out his wrath
upon this earth, he is not going to hurt
them like he's not going to hurt us.
Verse 13, 9 and verse 13. Go ahead. And
the sixth angel sounded. And I heard a
voice from the four horns of the golden
altar which is before God, saying to the
sixth angel which had the trumpet,
"Loose the four angels which are bound
in the great river Euphrates." Who are
these four? These are the four that he
told to hold back the four wind, didn't
it?
>> Yes, sir. And don't let nothing hurt it
until he seal his servant. Who are these
also? These four out of four carpenter
sisters involved.
>> Yes, sir.
And these are the four angels that was
riding them horses
because these are the ones the Lord
using to keep this earth under control.
Go ahead and read 15. And the four
angels were loosed which were prepared
FOR AN HOUR AND a day and a month and a
year for to slay the third part of men.
Look, it said the Euphrates River. They
was bound in the Euphrates River. and
we're going to show you the book talking
about the Euphrates River dried up.
People say, "Well, you know, it's dried
up now." I said, "That is not the
point." The point is everybody east of
the Euphrates River is going to be
against the one that the Lord going to
bring against Babylon the Great. That is
the point.
And the angel was loose. What verse were
we? We just finished 15. And the angel
was loose, which was prepared for an
hour and a day and a month and a year to
slay the third part of men. Can you
imagine that? This is just one side.
The third part of men. How many men is
it on the earth? That's counting
females, too.
Anybody know? They say 8 billion. 8
billion. What's a third of 8 billion?
That's two billion.
That's going to happen at that time.
Sisters and brother, are you ready for
that kind of killing?
What verse we had? 16. Go ahead. And the
number of the army of the horsemen were
200,000,000.
200 million soldiers.
That let me know that is more than
Russia. You got to have every nation
that's east of the Euphrates River. All
of them going to come under the banner
of Russia. America don't know that yet,
but we know it because we read the book.
>> Yes.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> And I heard the number of them. And thus
I saw the horses in the vision and them
that sat on them HAVING BREASTPLATES OF
FIRE and of jinth and brimstone. And the
heads of the horses were as the heads of
lions. Huh? And out of their mouth they
shoot you fire and smoke and brimstone.
Look, John was struggling trying to
identify these. You ever heard a horse
with a with a with with a head of a
lion? And you ever seen a lion with fire
come out of his mouth? He saw weapons
and he saw muzzle blast. And what
happened? Go ahead. By these three was
the third part of men killed by the fire
and by the smoke and by the brimstone
which issued out of their mouths. And
this is just from Eastern Europe kill a
third part of me. This ain't counting
what Western Europe going to do.
And you ain't ready for this.
This is all future. And the prophet
Zachchariah
prophesied it. That's why he's had these
angels hold back the four winds until
that time come. Now that's what's going
to happen. Just to tell you what's going
to happen when the Euphrates dried up.
Let's go into Revelation 16 and verse
12. 16 is 12. See, we ain't concerned
about the Euphrates River. The Euphrates
River is what separate east and western
Europe. Yes. So everybody that's east of
Europe
is going to come across that Euphrates.
from right across Turkey because the
Euphrates River run through Turkey.
>> Yes, sir.
Revelation 16
and we're going to start reading
at verse 12. 16 and 12.
Okay, go ahead.
>> And the six angels poured out his vow
upon the great river Euphrates.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the WATER THEREOF WAS DRIED UP.
>> That the way of the kings of the east
might be prepared.
>> The kings of what?
>> The kings of the east. What's east of
Turkey? China, Russia. There you go.
Poland, all them that think that they
western. That's why Russia is putting
their house in order to now like a
Ukraine and all that is east of the
Euphrates and they putting their house
in order cuz all of them going to come
across
and they going to come killing. They
going to kill a third part of men. Go
ahead and read verse 13. And I saw three
unclean spirits like frogs come out of
the mouth of the dragon and out of the
mouth of the beast and out of the mouth
of the false prophet. Now, how can you
have unclean spirit in the mouth of
Satan being he's unclean spirit? That's
talking about that conversation bringing
you know how it is what make wall James
says in nature and and enforce this the
uh uh nature and the you know the
tongue. Yes. So they talking words.
That's what these frogs are. Go ahead
and read.
>> 14. For they are the spirits of devils,
working miracles, which go forth unto
the kings of the earth and of the whole
world. Go ahead.
>> To gather them to to the battle of that
great day of God Almighty. Oh, so this
is God's battle, ain't it?
>> Yes. They don't know that.
This is what you call the battle war of
Armageddon. Keep reading. Behold, I come
as a thief. Blessed is he that watchth
and keepeth his garments, lest he walk
naked, and they see his shame. Look, the
world is naked. Now,
>> they don't know this. Everybody telling
you, you going to heaven, but the Lord
is talking about coming here, and he's
coming here to do great violence on this
earth.
Not sweet Jesus. Yeah. Yeah. That's who
we talking about. Go ahead and read. and
he gathered them together into a place
called in the Hebrew tongue Armageddon.
Now you done heard some y'all done heard
now and then somebody talk about
Armageddon, right? But that's is the
coming of Jesus and he going to come and
he is going to kill a whole lot of
people
because when he bring them across
he going to bring them across Western
Europe them 10 toes then the Lord
himself is going to enter in this battle
like it said in Revelation the 19th
chapter
that's going to bring the Lord
Because he said if he don't there will
be no flesh saved cuz they going to come
waving nuclear weapons and everything.
Ain't nobody got an arsenal of nuclear
weapons and you losing and you going to
just lose. No, you going to bring out
the biggest weapon you got. Right.
And all the Europeans got nuclear
weapon. That's right.
They going to bring them up. Then that's
when the Lord's going to intervene. And
here he come. Let's go into Zechariah
the 14th chapter.
Zechariah chapter 14. These sisters and
brothers, these people are playing
tomorrow
that's going to show up tomorrow at
church. They are playing with this
thing. But Zechariah call it
Zechariah chapter 14. That's why it's
titled the pro, you know, the gospel by
the prophet Zechariah. This is the
gospel.
We're going to start reading at verse
one. Zechariah 14 and verse one.
Okay, go ahead. Behold the day of the
Lord cometh and thy spo shall be divided
in the midst of thee. That's the day of
the Lord. That's the day of the Lord
going coming in this earth and he going
to kill a lot of people. That's why it
says the spoil shall divide in the midst
of thee. What happen when you go to war?
You take the spores, don't you?
>> That's right, Reed.
>> For I will gather all nations.
>> How many nations?
>> All of them.
>> Go ahead.
>> Against Jerusalem to battle.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And the city shall be taken. Go ahead.
>> And the houses rifled. Go ahead.
>> And the women ravished. Go ahead.
>> And half of the city shall go forth into
captivity. Go ahead. And the residue of
the people shall not be cut off from the
city. That's what I tell people. Do not
go to Jerusalem now. Especially now this
thing is up on top of is upon us. Yes.
Cuz when he bring Russia and all our
allies cross that Euphrates River, they
why they going to Jerusalem? Because
Western Europe is going to install the
pope
and the temple that they going to be
that the over there going to
build in Jerusalem. And the pope is
really the one that's gonna be calling
the shot because he said that this woman
was riding the beast.
>> That's right.
>> So the one that's riding the horse,
ain't he the one that's controlling it,
>> controlling it
>> in the name of religion, sisters and
brothers.
Go ahead and read verse three. THEN
SHALL THE LORD GO FORTH and fight
against those nations as when he fought
in the day of battle, and his feet shall
stand in that day upon the Mount of
Olives.
>> You mean the Lord's feet are going to
stand on the Mount of Olives? Yes, sir.
He ain't going to
poof rapture you off the earth.
>> Uh-uh. He's coming here and by the time
his feet hit the Mount of Olives,
they're going to be dead bodies
everywhere.
>> What verse
>> we had? Four.
>> Go ahead. And his feet shall stand in
that day upon the mount of olives which
is before Jerusalem on the east. And the
mount of olives shall cleave in the
midst thereof toward the east and toward
the west. And there shall be a very
great valley. And half of the mountain
shall remove toward the north and half
of it toward the south. See Jesus coming
in his strength and all the angels with
him and all the people in the first
resurrection. when his feet hit that
mount of olives.
>> Yeah,
>> it's gonna split because the power is
going to drop on it. But go ahead and
read.
>> And you shall flee to the valley of the
mountains. For the valley of the
mountains shall reach unto As you shall
flee like you fled from before the
earthquake in the days of Isaiah, KING
OF JUDAH. WHY is it that the servant of
God going to be running? Because that
beast and far probably going to inflict
some real pain on the servant of God.
And you gonna know what's going on when
you see the Lord come.
>> Yes, sir.
>> You gonna know that is the Lord when his
feet hit that mountain. Yes, sir. Then
you gonna run to him
>> because now you see your savior is here.
Go ahead and read.
>> AND THE LORD MY GOD shall come and all
the saints with you.
>> And the Lord my God shall come and all
the saints with thee. Where did he get
these saints? They murdered HIM IN THE
AIR.
>> YES.
But in case you talking about thinking
about this is talking about the father
going to come with the saints, let me
straighten you out.
>> Let's go into first Thessalonians the
third chapter.
>> Straighten it out.
>> 1 Thessalonians the third chapter. Cuz
that made Jesus a powder puff.
He loved everybody.
The thief, the murderer,
the homosexual.
I tell how can somebody be punished and
they can't help? I said if the Lord
going to punish you, that tell me that
they can help it.
How come you don't get you you broke and
you ain't got you can't pay rent and you
can't buy grocer? How come you don't get
your pistol and walk up to the nearest
bank and stick it up
>> cuz you don't want to get shot to go to
jail?
>> If you knew the consequences, you can
straighten anything. Yeah, you can.
straight it out. So let's look
who this God is that's coming with all
his saints. Three and 1 Thessalonians
the uh 3rd chapter and verse two
verse
>> three and two
>> 12 I'm I'm sorry uh 3 and 12 3 and 12
okay read. And the Lord make you to
increase and abound in love one toward
another and toward all men, even as we
do toward you.
>> Uhhuh.
>> To the end he may establish your hearts
unblameable and holiness before God even
our father.
>> At what time?
>> At the coming of our Lord JESUS CHRIST
WITH ALL HIS SAINTS. So you know that
Zechariah 14 chapter is talking about
Jesus, don't you? It is his feet that
going to when it hit the mountain, it's
going to split.
He going to come with all his saints.
And I mean, and that's going to the
saints are the ones going to meet him in
the first resurrection. And when he
come, sisters and brothers, he is coming
to do some damage. Let's go into
Zechariah the 12th chapter. Zechariah
told it all to you, sisters and
brothers. Yeah, he did. All you got to
do is listen to Zechariah like all the
other prophets told it to you. But you
don't read prophecy because somebody
told you, well, you know, you're a New
Testament Christian. That old stuff
didn't happen.
I bet ain't none of this happened.
Zechariah 12 and we're going to start
reading at verse two. Zechariah 12 and
verse two.
And this prophet saw it all. The Lord
showed it to him. Verse two, go ahead
and read. Behold, I will make Jerusalem
a CUP OF TREMBLING UNTO ALL the people
round about.
>> I mean, every it's going to be a cup of
trembling because what's going to go
down in Jerusalem? To all the people
round about. Go ahead and read.
>> When they shall be in the siege both
against Judah and against Jerusalem.
>> Go ahead.
>> And in that day will I make Jerusalem a
burdensome stone for all people. All
that burn themselves with it shall be
cut in pieces. Look, the Lord said all
that burden himself with Jerusalem
are going to be cut in pieces because
the Lord is coming to do some real
damage. Go ahead. Though all the people
of the earth be gathered together
against it.
>> So he's going to bring all armies
against it cuz this is World War II,
sisters and brothers. Skip down to verse
nine. Skip down to verse nine
and go ahead. And it shall come to pass
in that day that I will seek to destroy
all the nations that come against
Jerusalem.
>> Right. This is this is Jesus going to do
this. Not sweet cuddly Jesus.
>> No, Jesus going to do it.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> And I will pour upon the house of David
and upon the inhabitants of Jerusalem
THE SPIRIT OF GRACE. GO AHEAD.
>> And of supplications, and they shall
look upon me whom they have pierced.
>> Wait a minute.
>> You mean they fears the father?
No.
>> You mean this is sweet Jesus?
>> This is him.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> THEY SHALL LOOK UPON ME WHOM THEY have
pierced and they shall mourn for him as
one mourning for his only son. They're
going to be doing more mourning for the
self. Go ahead and read.
>> AND SHALL BE IN BITTERNESS FOR HIM as
one that is in bitterness for his
firstborn
>> cuz he is the firstborn. Go ahead and
read. In that day shall there be a great
morning in Jerusalem.
>> Uhhuh. At the mount of Hatterim hadum in
the valley of Megado. I mean a great cuz
that's the Armageddon. That's the valley
of Megado.
Great morning sisters and brothers
because it going to be a whole lot of
killing. And it said they shall look
upon me whom they appear.
>> Yes sir. I tell you, Jesus, but I'm
going to let you go and read it. Let's
go into Romans. I'm in Revelation the
first chapter. We want you to read
everything because you have been
woefully misinformed
by ministers that are misinformed.
Nobody bothers to check anything. They
just follow what they've been told.
That's it.
Revelation chapter 1
and we're going to read verse one and we
going to skip Revelation 1 and verse
one. Go ahead and read the revelation of
Jesus CHRIST WHICH GOD GAVE UNTO HIM.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> TO SHOW unto his servants things which
must surely come to pass and he sent and
signified it by his angel unto his
servant John.
>> So this revelation is to show you what's
going to come in the future. ministers
keep you out of Revelation, but skip
down to verse seven. Verse seven and
read it.
>> Behold, he cometh with clouds, and every
eye shall see him.
eye going to see him. Go ahead and read.
>> And they also which pierced him, and all
kindreds of the earth SHALL WHAIL
BECAUSE OF HIM.
>> And they that pierced him going to see
him, and inhabits on earth are going to
well because of him. When you well, that
mean you in pain, ain't you? That's
right. Drama is coming upon you and you
keep telling me I'll be glad when Christ
come. Do will you?
>> So let's go back to show you some of the
stuff that's going to happen. Back to
Zechariah the 14th chapter. This
Zechariah told it, sister.
>> He told it.
All you got to do is read it. And he
ain't the only one. I just picked the
prophet to bring the gospel out of. I
could have brought this gospel out of
Daniel. I could have brought it out of
Jeremiah. Yes, sir. I could have brought
it out of Isaiah. I could have I just
chose the Lord put it on my on my mind
and just choose Daniel to show you
either way it go all I'mma telling the
same story.
The Lord said, "I'm coming to this earth
and I'm going whoop head
and take it over
and ain't nothing you can do about it.
>> Nothing."
>> Zechariah 14 and verse 6. 14 and six.
Okay, go ahead.
>> And it shall come to pass in that day,
>> In that day, go ahead.
>> That the light shall not be clear nor
dark.
>> Uhhuh. But it shall be one day which
shall be known to the Lord, nor day, not
day nor night, but it shall come to pass
that at evening time it shall be like.
We ain't never seen a day like that,
right?
>> But the Lord going to create a day that
we ain't ever seen. Go ahead and read.
>> And it shall be in that day that living
waters shall go out from Jerusalem.
>> Half of them toward the former sea and
half of them toward the hinder sea. in
summer and in winter shall it be. And
that's the that's when the Lord is set
up on this earth. That is his cleansing.
He going to use water that's going to
come out from under his temple
which the rubel and his kohar is going
to build and this water is going to
cleanse the whole earth cuz this earth
is polluted under man.
>> Yes.
>> Go ahead and read. AND THE LORD SHALL BE
KING over all the earth and heaven. All
the earth. Over all the earth. Go ahead.
In that day shall there be one Lord and
his name one. Ain't going to be all this
Buddha and and all this other stuff.
>> One God and his name one. What name is
that? That's the name that he came in
his father's name. Yes. Jesus. Skip now
to verse 12. Verse 12 and go ahead. And
this shall be the plague wherewith the
Lord will smite all the people that have
fought against Jerusalem.
>> Go ahead.
>> Their flesh shall consume away while
they stand upon their feet.
>> And their eyes shall consume away and
their holes and their tongue shall
consume away in their mouth. Can you
even imagine something like that, man?
You standing there, all of a sudden you
done turned to a skeleton
and the bones fall to the ground.
No, brother. This can't be coming out of
the Bible. Yes, it is. Keep reading. And
it shall come to pass in that day that a
great tomorrow from the Lord shall be
among them.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And they shall lay hold everyone on the
head of his neighbor, and his HAND SHALL
RISE UP AGAINST THE HAND of his
neighbor. So they're going to turn man
against man. The Lord did that already.
But when Esau,
Moab, and Amar was coming against Judea,
yes, the Lord
made and it was all allies.
The Lord made the two brothers.
Amma
turn
against Esau.
See, Moab and Ammon are lost children.
Yes, they all allied to go and jump
Judah. The Lord put that mingle spirit
in there. The two brothers look at one
another. What are we doing with this
stranger which is our They jumped and
killed him to the ground. Now once they
killed all the Edomite, then they turn
on one another.
>> He did
>> and kill him. And one not one man was
left living.
That's what's going to happen with all
them armies that go up to fight against
Jerusalem. Brother Bo, that's scary. But
it's the truth. Skip now to 16
and go ahead. And it shall come to pass
that everyone that is left of ALL THE
NATIONS WHICH CAME up against Jerusalem
shall even go up from year to year to
worship the king the Lord of hosts and
to keep the feast of tabernacles.
>> See everybody laughing at these feasts
we keeping now but once the Lord there
you going to keep them especially
tabernacle. Go ahead and read. And it
shall be that whosoever will not come up
of all the families of the earth unto
Jerusalem to worship the king, the Lord
of hosts, eat upon them shall be no
rain. If you ain't get no rain on your
crop, what's going to happen to your
crop? Star.
>> You going it ain't going to grow and you
ain't going to have nothing to eat and
you going to starve to death. That mean
all the nations going to go up
and keep tabernacle. Probably all of
them. But I can only say tabernacle cuz
this is what the book say. Now let's go
and this is Zachchariah told you this
sisters and brothers. Let's go into
Matthews the 21st chapter.
Matthews chapter 21.
>> Please make it plain because sisters and
brothers, the Lord want us to know this.
That's why he had all these prophets
preach the same gospel.
Ain't nobody listening.
But they going to listen. But it's going
to be kind of late now.
Just like you're jumping off a building
like Sears Tower. All of a sudden, you
change your mind. Too late now.
You in full.
That's right. You better change your
mind before you jump.
Now's the time to change your mind and
your ways and your behavior.
Find out what God's laws are and keep
them. And you should know cuz we read
them to you every Sabbath day. 21.
Matthews 21 and1. Okay, go ahead. And
when they drew near unto Jerusalem, and
were come to Beth up to the Mount of
Olives, then sent Jesus two disciples,
saying unto them, see he stopped at
Mount of Olives because that's the first
place his feet going to hit when he
come.
>> So he stopped there. Then he sent his
two disciples. Go ahead and read. saying
unto them, "Go into the village over
against you, and straightway you shall
find an ass tied and a coat wither." Go
ahead.
>> Loose them, and breed them unto me.
>> Uhhuh.
>> And if any man say unto you, unto you,
you shall say, The Lord had need of
them. Go ahead.
>> And straightway he will send them.
>> Go ahead. ALL THIS WAS DONE THAT IT
MIGHT BE FULFILLED WHICH WAS spoken by
the prophet, saying, Tell ye the
daughter of Zion, behold, thy king
cometh unto thee, meek, and sitting upon
an ass, and a coke, the fold of an ass.
>> Oh, sir, ain't your personal savior.
Huh? Thy king, he's the king of of
Israel.
Go ahead and read. And the disciples
went and did as Jesus commanded them,
and brought the ass and the coat, and
put on them their clothes, and they set
him of their own. And a very great
multitude spread their garments in the
way. Others cut down branches from the
trees and straw them in the way. Now,
that's where you get Ash Wednesday from.
>> What you say? Palm Sunday.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, then. Well, excuse me. I ain't too
versed in the Catholic religion.
Well, Palm Sunday there. No, Ash
Wednesday is with the mark of the beast.
Okay. All right. Keep going. Verse N.
And the multitude that went before and
that followed CRIED SAYING, HOSANA TO
THE SON OF DAVID, blessed is he that
cometh in the name OF THE LORD. HOSANA
IN THE HIGHEST. SO, we're going to look
at this. He said, as it is written, who
wrote about it? Zechariah. Let's go to
Zechariah the ninth chapter
cuz he told the story, sister.
>> He told it.
Zechariah the 9th chapter and we're
going to start reading at verse 9.
Zechariah chapter 9 and verse 9.
Zechariah 9 and 9.
Go ahead.
>> REJOICE GREATLY, oh daughter of Zion.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> SHOUT, OH DAUGHTER OF JERUSALEM.
>> UHHUH.
>> BEHOLD, THY KING COMETH UNTO THEE. He is
just and having salvation, lowly and
riding upon an ass, and upon a coat, THE
FOLD OF AN ASS. NOW, because what we
just read, we know for sure that this is
talking about Jesus, ain't it?
>> For sure. But look at it. What else he
going to do for sure? Read the next
verse.
>> And I will cut off the chariot from
Ephraim. Uhhuh. And the horse from
Jerusalem. Go ahead. And the battle boat
shall be cut off. And he shall speak
peace unto the heathen.
>> Yeah. And they going to listen too cuz
he could be whoop their head. Go ahead
and read.
>> And his dominion shall be from sea even
to sea and from the river even to the
ends of the earth.
>> Dominion. That mean he going to dominate
this whole earth.
>> Yes. ain't going to be a place on this
earth that Jesus ain't going to be
ruling at that time. Him and all his
saints. You make that first resurrection
sister and brothers, something go wrong
somewhere else. The Lord ain't going to
have to say go look at it. You going to
be God too and you going to know his
thought and you going to go
in the most remote part of the earth.
What you doing?
You better walk this way. Don't turn to
the left or to the right.
Let's back up to Zechariah 19, the n
second chapter rather. Zechariah chapter
2. Just showing you sisters and brothers
that the prophets all of them preached
the gospel of the king coming of the
kingdom of God. That is the gospel.
Zechariah 2 and one. Two and one. Okay.
Go ahead. I LIFTED UP MINE EYES AGAIN,
and looked, and behold, a man with a
measuring line in his hand.
>> Go ahead.
>> Then said I, whether goest thou, and he
said unto me, to measure Jerusalem
>> to see what is the breath thereof, and
what is the length thereof?
>> Go ahead.
>> And behold, the angel that talked with
me went forth, and another angel went
out to meet him.
>> So now he's getting ready to bring us
back now. So he's married in Jerusalem.
So the angel went to inform another. Go
ahead and read. And he said unto him,
"RUN, SPEAK TO THIS YOUNG MAN, SAYING,
Jerusalem shall be inhabited as towns
without walls for the multitude of men
and cattle therein." Now, Jerusalem is
inhabited now, but it's by the wrong
people.
>> But it's talking about us now.
>> Yes. Go ahead.
>> For I, sayeth the Lord, will be unto her
a WALL OF FIRE ROUND ABOUT. I'mma be
around a fire roundabout. Go ahead. AND
WE'LL BE THE GLORY IN THE MIDST OF HER.
>> I'm going to be the glory in the midst
of her. Meaning he going to be in
Jerusalem, sister and brother. Jews are
back. Yeah. Let's go over there and talk
to Jesus. Yes.
Think about it.
Skip down to verse seven. Verse seven
and go ahead. Deliver thyself, O Zion.
>> Go ahead.
>> That dwelleth with the daughter of
Babylon. So you got to make two
deliverance. First thing, you got to
deliver yourself out of this Babylonian
false teaching that's called the world
called Christianity. And then when it's
time to flee, you got to be smart enough
to know when the Lord going to give you
some
>> transportation. You don't need money.
You don't need passport.
All you going to need is knowledge and
be clean.
The Lord going to take you here.
>> What verse is that?
>> We at verse eight.
>> Go ahead.
>> For thus sayeth the Lord of hosts, after
the glory hath he sent me unto THE
NATIONS WHICH SPOILED YOU.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> FOR HE that toucheth YOU TOUCHETH THE
APPLE OF HIS EYE. After the glory have
he sent me, this is Jesus talking. Who
is he that sent him?
>> The father.
So that mean that we Israel is the apple
of the father's eye. Yes, sir. Well,
that's big. That's a great big
promotion, ain't it?
>> And these nations are messing over us.
>> That's why you see all this killing.
What verse we had? Nine.
>> Go ahead.
>> For behold, I WILL SHAKE MINE HAND UPON
THEM.
>> GO AHEAD. and they shall be a spoil to
their servants and you shall know that
the Lord of hosts HAVE SENT ME. WE GOING
TO KNOW because we going first thing we
going to look at him and he going to
Jesus going to look just like us
>> black and nappy hair
right all of a sudden
it's just like you beating up a little
old bitty boy
and then his big brother show up
7'8
and you 3' n you know what's going to
happen to you.
>> Our big brother, what verse
>> we at 10.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> Sing and rejoice, oh daughter of Zion.
Go ahead.
>> For lo, I come and I will dwell in the
midst of thee, sayeth the Lord.
>> He going to dwell in Jerusalem. He keep
telling you that. Go ahead and read.
>> And many nations shall be joined to the
LORD IN THAT DAY. Go ahead.
>> And shall be my people. And I will dwell
in the midst of thee. and thou shalt
know that the Lord OF HOSTS HAS SENT ME
unto thee. He keep telling you the
father sent me. He sent me to do a job.
He sent me to do a job.
Let's go into St. John the 6th chapter.
St. John 6th chapter.
See, people take issue sometime when
you, you know, when you tell them we
Israel and we this, we, you know, who do
they think they are? We are the people
that God chose. Yep.
>> It's good to know that, but then again,
when you know why we got into captivity,
it's a shame.
>> We didn't have to go through what we
going through.
>> No, we didn't.
>> All we had to do was obey God and use
his word. That's why I don't walk walk
around thumping my chest. Uh-uh.
I know the whole story.
I am not here because the Lord just
thought he Well, I think I'm going to
punish him for something. Uh-uh. I'm
here because I misbehaved. I misbehaved.
So, what do I have to thump my chest
for? Uh-uh.
that the Lord going to come
because he was sent and he keep telling
you that
6 and35 St. John 6 and verse 35
read it and Jesus said unto them I am
the bread of life.
>> Go ahead.
>> He that cometh to me shall never hunger
>> and he that believeth on me shall never
thirst
>> cuz he is the one. Skip down to verse 38
and continue.
>> For I came down from HEAVEN NOT TO DO MY
own will but the will of him that sent
me. That's the father
>> whom we are the apple of his eye.
>> Go ahead. I cannot do my will own will
but the will of him that sent me. Go
ahead and read. AND THIS IS THE FATHER'S
WILL WHICH HAVE SENT ME. This is the
father's will which have sent me. Jesus
letting us know I didn't come on my own.
And you got preachers running around
like they somebody.
If Jesus said I was sent, then who are
you? Go ahead and read that of all which
you have given me, I should lose
nothing, but should raise it up again at
the last day. But you bring them on to
the heaven right now. Raise it up again
five minutes after they die. at the last
day.
>> at the last day. Keep reading.
>> And this is the will of him that sent
me.
>> Go ahead and read.
>> That everyone which seeth the son and
believeth on him,
>> Go ahead.
>> may have everlasting life. Go ahead.
>> AND I WILL RAISE HIM UP at the last day.
And I'll raise him up at the last day.
Not only is he offering you a return to
the land, he is offering you
immortality.
>> Yes, sir.
How can you not pay attention to this
God?
>> What verse we have? 44. Skip down to
verse 44 and read. No man can come to me
EXCEPT THE FATHER WHICH HAVE SENT me
draw him.
>> Except the father which has sent me.
>> Draw him. Go ahead and read.
>> And I will raise him up at the last day.
Isn't that kind of contrary to what
you've been taught in church?
If he going to raise him up at the last
day, then why are the dead folks?
>> In the grave. They in the grave.
Let's go in Isaiah 48.
Isaiah chapter 48.
Because the prophets
told it all.
>> We just come by way of Zechariah today.
I could bring this same message by way
of Jeremiah
or Ezekiel
because the prophets told the whole
story. Once the prophets got through
prophesying, there was nothing left to
prophesy.
That's why the New Testament is a
testimony of Jesus.
>> Yes.
And the testimony of Jesus is the spirit
which is the word of prophecy. Yes.
Y'all understand?
>> And people tell me you New Testament
Christian so they can hear you up in
there and feed you with the Gentile
doctrine and take your life away from
you, your eternal life.
Verse 12, go ahead. Hearken unto me, oh
Jacob and Israel, my cult. Go ahead.
>> I am he.
>> Uhhuh. I am the first. I also am the
last. I'm here. I'm He. I want you all
to listen to me. I'm the first and I'm
the last. I'm the first God you ever
encountered. And as flesh and blood
people, I will be the last God that you
will encounter. When the father show up,
there won't be no such species as man.
But we don't know that because we don't
read the book. Go ahead and read. My
hand also have laid the foundations of
the earth. Go ahead. and my right hand
has spanned the heavens. Go ahead. WHEN
I CALL UNTO THEM, THEY stand up
together. Now, if average person is not
informed, he would THINK THIS IS THE
FATHER TALKING, wouldn't it?
>> But then this let us know that this is
not the father talking. Skip down to
verse 16. Verse 16 and read it. Come you
near unto me. Uh-huh. Hear you this. Go
ahead.
>> I HAVE NOT SPOKEN IN SECRET FROM THE
BEGINNING. UH-HUH. From the time that it
was, there am I. There was I am I am I?
Go ahead and read. And now the Lord God
and his spirit HAS SENT ME ACCORDING to
what we've been reading. Who is this?
Jesus.
The prophets called it all.
Tell you what else Zechariah call. Let's
go into Zechariah the fourth chapter.
Zechariah the 4th chapter, we're going
to start reading at verse one.
I mean, all of God's prophets knew about
the end time. That's and what's going to
happen. That's why nowadays all of God's
servants know about the end time. We
know what's going to happen. We know it
because we are servants of God.
We're going to walk in his law so he
won't take it away from us. We know
Zechariah 4 and one. Go ahead and read.
And the angel that talked with me came
again and wake me as a man that is
waking out of his sleep. Go ahead.
>> And he said unto me, WHAT SEEEST THOU?
UHHUH.
>> And I said, I have looked, and behold, a
candlestick all of gold with a bowl upon
the top of it. Go ahead. and his seven
lamps thereon and seven pipes to the
seven lamps which are upon the top
thereof. Now these he just defining the
throne rule of Jesus. Yes. When you go
in there you see these seven lamps.
Those are the seven angels which are the
seven spirits of God that run to and fro
in the earth and report on you.
Go ahead and read verse three. And two
olive trees by it. one up on the right
hand of the bowl and the other up on the
left side thereof.
>> So now we got two olive trees. Skip down
to verse 11. Verse 11 and go ahead.
>> Then answered I and said unto him, what
are these two olive trees upon the right
side of the candlestick and upon the
left side thereof?
>> He wanted to know. Go ahead and read.
And I answered again and said unto him,
"What feed these two olive branches
which through the two golden pipes empty
the golden oil out of themselves?"
>> That's the word of God. Word of God came
out of them. Go ahead and read.
>> And he answered me and said, "Knowest
thou not what these be?"
>> Go ahead.
>> And I said, "No, my Lord."
>> Go ahead. Then said he, "These are the
two anointed ones that stand by the Lord
of the whole earth." Now, let's go and
find out who these are. Let's go into
Revelation 11 chapter.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Revelation 11 chapter. I'm talking about
this this prophet Zechariah. He told it,
didn't he? He told it. Ain't nobody
fooling around here.
Revelation chapter 11.
And we're going to start reading verse
one. Revelation chapter 11 and verse
one. We learn a whole lot of stuff here
on our way to learning something.
Okay, read it. And there was given me a
reed like unto a rod. And the angel
stood, saying, Rise, and measure the
temple of God, and the altar, and them
that worship therein.
>> Go ahead.
>> But the court which is without the
temple, leave out. Go ahead.
>> And measure it not. For it is given unto
the Gentiles, and the holy city shall
they tread underfoot 40 and two months.
Now, there's two things we just learned
here. First thing is temple. that the
river bell them build is not
is is on the real temple site. Yes. But
the temple that Edom's going to build.
Yes. Which the pulp is going to move in.
It's going to be built in the court way.
God don't even want the this false
prophet to set in the TEMPLE ON THE SPOT
where his temple is going to be.
>> Go ahead and read verse three. AND I
WILL GIVE POWER UNTO MY two witnesses.
>> And he going to give power unto his two
witnesses. Go ahead and read.
>> And they shall prophesy a thousand 2003
score days clotheing sackcloth.
>> So they going to prophesy for three and
a half years. All the time this guy
doing miracles and stuff. God got to put
him a balancer there.
>> Cuz if he don't have a balancer there,
the world be eating these this false
prophet up because the Lord going to let
him let Satan give him the power to do
miracles. Cause fire to come down from
heaven. Cause a statue to walk. Go ahead
and read verse four. These are the two
olive trees and the two candlesticks
standing before the God of the earth.
Oh, so now we know
who these guys that Zachariah mentioned
though. Yes. Too high of a tree. These
are two men that's going to be here. Go
ahead and read. And if any man will hurt
them, uh, fire proceeded out of their
mouth and devour their enemies. And if
any man will hurt them, he must in this
manner be killed. Them guys going to
have some power, ain't they?
>> Go ahead and read.
>> These have power to shut heaven that it
rain not in the days of their prophecy.
Go ahead.
>> And have power over waters to turn them
to blood.
>> Go ahead. and to smite the earth with
all plagues as often as they will. Now,
Gentiles teaching, well, you know,
that's Moses and Elijah. That is not
Moses and Elijah.
>> No, it is not. There are flesh and blood
men that's living nowadays and probably
living now.
>> Brother ask me, boy, don't you want? No,
I don't want to be one of them. I want
to be in the wilderness. I'm doing my
labor now. Right.
>> What verse we Verse seven.
>> Go ahead.
>> And when they shall HAVE FINISHED THEIR
TESTIMONY, THE beast that ascended out
of the bottom of the pit shall make war
against them and shall overcome them and
kill them. So the pope of the European
Union going to kill these two witnesses.
That's prior to the coming of the Lord.
But skip down to verse 11 and go ahead.
And after three days and A HALF, THE
SPIRIT OF LIFE FROM GOD ENTERED unto
them, and they stood upon their feet,
and great fear fell upon them which saw
them.
>> Now Lord brought them back to life. And
what did he say? Go ahead and read.
>> And they heard a great voice from
heaven, saying up to unto them, come up
here.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And they ascended up to heaven in a
cloud, and their enemies beheld them.
>> Now people say, see, they went to
heaven. No, let's keep reading. Now,
skip now. What's going to happen
quickly? Verse 15, read it. And the
seventh angel sounded, and there were
great voices in heaven, saying, "The
kingdoms of this world ARE BECOME THE
KINGDOMS OF our Lord and of his Christ,
and he shall reign forever and ever."
Now, let's see what's going to happen
when that seven trumpet is blown. Let's
go into First Thessalonians, the 4th
chapter. 1 Thessalonians, the 4th
chapter. And we got one more place after
this. 1 Thessalonians chapter 4. The
Lord laid this thing out. You don't have
you won't have no excuse when you stand
before him.
And if you get this thing right, then
you don't have to stand before him.
This is what people don't understand.
You don't have to be stand before the
Lord on judgment day, right? They going
to be standing before you with the Lord.
>> I don't want to be the judge. I want to
be the judge. the judge.
>> 1 Thessalonians 4 and verse 13. 4 and
13. Go ahead.
>> But I would not have you to be ignorant,
brethren.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Concerning them which are asleep.
>> Go ahead.
>> That you sorrow not even as others which
have no hope.
>> See, look. Lord, look. If somebody been
walking in God laws and keeping his
commandments,
>> Yes.
>> and they done been baptized into Jesus.
If it's a male and circumcised law, if
they die, why you going to grieve over
them? They better than you
>> cuz now they dead. THEY CAN'T GET CUT
OFF. But as long as you breathing, you
can get cut off. That is right.
Just hope you be as clean as them when
you go. Go ahead and read. FOR IF WE
BELIEVE THAT JESUS DIED and rose again,
even so them also which sleep in Jesus
will God bring with them.
>> And we believe that. Go ahead and read.
>> FOR THIS WE SAY UNTO YOU BY THE WORD OF
THE LORD. By the word of the Lord, the
prophet told you, go ahead,
>> that we which are alive and remain until
the coming of the Lord shall not prevent
them which are asleep.
>> We ain't going to get in that way. Go
ahead and read.
>> For the Lord himself shall descend from
heaven WITH A SHOUT.
>> COME UP HERE.
>> YES, SIR.
>> With the voice of the archangel and WITH
THE TRUMPET OF GOD.
>> Go ahead.
>> And the dead IN CHRIST SHALL RISE FIRST.
right along with them two witnesses
teach
the dead in Christ shall rise first and
go ahead and read. THEN WE WHICH ARE
ALIVE and remain shall be caught up
together with them in the clouds to meet
the Lord in the air. And so shall we
ever be with the Lord.
>> And we know that he's coming back to
this earth, don't we?
>> Yes, sir.
We shall be with him forever on this
earth. That's when the Lord come back
cuz he going to Jerusalem. Let's go to
last place. Zechariah the 8th chapter.
That mean that Zechariah told it,
sister.
>> He told it.
>> He didn't he didn't hold back. That's
why people don't understand. You going
to tell me what prophecy has been
fulfilled? That let me know you haven't
read nothing.
You only listen to somebody. Cuz if you
read something, you would have run into
some something that was contrary to what
you've been talking about about going to
heaven.
Zechariah 8, we're going to start
reading at verse one. Zechariah 8 and
verse one. Go ahead and read again. THE
WORD OF THE LORD of hosts came to me
saying, "Thus said the Lord of hosts, I
was jealous for Zion with great
jealousy, and I was jealous for her with
great fury."
>> I told you, go ahead and read. Thus
sayeth the Lord, I AM RETURNED UNTO
ZION.
>> I will return.
>> I am returned.
>> I am returned unto Zion. Go ahead.
>> And will dwell in the midst of
Jerusalem.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And Jerusalem shall BE CALLED A CITY OF
truth and the mountain of the Lord of
hosts, the holy mountain.
>> That's why it's going to be the holy
government. Now skip down to verse seven
and go ahead. Thus said the Lord of
hosts. Behold, I will SAVE MY PEOPLE
FROM THE EAST COUNTRY and from the west
country. Go ahead. And I will bring
them, and they shall dwell in the midst
of Jerusalem, and they shall be my
people, and I will be their God in truth
AND IN RIGHTEOUSNESS. SEE, AIN'T NOBODY
SEE THE strangers of the Gentiles ain't
interested in this.
>> That's why they haven't taught you this.
>> But they don't understand that. So as it
go with Israel, it goes with them
because the whole earth is intertwined
with Israel and the God of Israel.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Skip down and read verse 13. Go ahead.
And it shall COME TO PASS THAT AS YOU
WERE A CURSED AMONG the heathen, oh
house of Judah and house of Israel. See,
you're a cursed among the heathen.
Nation don't like you. Don't nobody like
you. Nobody.
>> You don't even like you.
So as you were a curse among the among
the nations, go ahead and read.
>> Oh house of of Judah and house of
Israel, so will I save you and you shall
be a blessing. Fear not, but let your
hands be strong. He said, now just like
you was a curse, when I come, you going
to be a blessing
among the nation. I'm going show you how
much of a blessing.
Skip now to verse 20.
Verse 20 and go ahead. Thus sayeth the
Lord of hosts, IT SHALL YET COME TO PASS
THAT THERE SHALL COME PEOPLE AND THE
INHABITANTS OF MANY CITIES, and the
inhabitants of one city shall GO TO
ANOTHER, SAYING, LET US GO SPEEDILY TO
PRAY BEFORE THE LORD, and to seek the
Lord of hosts. I will all go also. Then
let's go where? to Jerusalem. We ain't
talking heaven now. Go ahead and read.
>> Yes.
>> These are many people and many strong
nations.
And let's go and seek your Lord and
worship before him. Go ahead and read.
>> Yeah. MANY STRONG MANY PEOPLE AND STRONG
NATIONS SHALL COME TO SEEK the Lord of
hosts in Jerusalem.
>> UHHUH.
>> AND TO PRAY BEFORE THE Lord cuz that's
where it's going to be. Go ahead.
>> Thus say the Lord of hosts.
>> Go ahead. In those days it shall come to
pass THAT 10 MEN SHALL TAKE HOLD out of
all languages of the nations. Even shall
take HOLD OF THE SKIRT OF HIM THAT IS a
Jew.
>> Wait a minute. 10 men out of every
nation going to take hold of the skirt
of him that's Jew.
>> Yeah. Why? GO AHEAD AND READ.
>> SAY we will go with you.
>> Uhhuh.
>> FOR WE HAVE HEARD THAT GOD IS WITH YOU.
Did you see it in that in 48 when they
gave our land to the
>> All of a sudden you that is the curse
and nobody want you around in their
community. You going to look around.
It's going TO BE A CROWD OF THEM COMING
BEHIND YOU.
>> We're going with you. You know what? We
probably take off running.
But in this time, they ain't coming to
hand you. They coming to go with you.
Because Jesus, the God of hosts, will be
in Jerusalem and that's where you on
your way. Yes, sir. So, Zachchariah,
preach the gospel
of the coming of the kingdom of God.
Yes, sir.
>> Thank you for your time.